Guide to the Vassar College Realia Collection, circa 1648-2020 (bulk 1818-2000)
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Series II. Vassariana, 1861-2020
  - Plastic Objects
    - VC Library coffee mug, undated (Box 18)
      Plastic travel mug with image of VC Library
  - Serveware
    - Serving plate - Alumnae House (?), silver, undated (Box 100)
      Silver serving plate with "AH" engraved into the rim. Likely from the Alumnae House.
    - Tray, undated (Box 13)
      Black metal serving tray with illustration of VC Main building.
    - Tray, 1915 (Box 62)
      small bronze-colored tray from the VC 50th anniversary
    - Tray, undated (Box 78)
      Plastic tray with an illustration of Main Building printed on it.
    - VC Chafing dish, silver, circa 1914 (Box 98)
      Round, silver chafing dish with stand, burner, 2 pans, and a lid with a Vassar College seal welded to it. Owned by Laura S. West (VC 1914).
    - VC Napkin ring, silver, undated (Box 22, Slot 32)
      VC napkin ring, silver w/ initials EBM
  - Silverware
    - Sugar tongs - Alumnae House (?), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      Silver sugar tongs with "AH" engraved in the handle. Most likely from the Alumnae House.
    - Vassar College fork, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
      Silver fork with "Vassar College" engraved on the handle.
    - Vassar Female College butter knives (8), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
      Silverplate
    - Vassar Female College fork, circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College fork, circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College forks (2), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
      Silverplate, round handle
    - Vassar Female College forks (9), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
      Silverplate, pointed handle
    - Vassar Female College knives (8), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College long handled salt spoons (2), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College sugar spoons, scalloped (3), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College table spoons (16), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College teaspoon, circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College teaspoon, circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - Vassar Female College teaspoon, circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
      VC spoon engraved with "Vassar Female College"
    - Vassar Female College teaspoons (10), circa 1861 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
    - VC butter knives, large (4), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      silver, VC logo on handle
    - VC butter knives, small (6), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
    - VC commerative teaspoons (2), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      sterling. Main building sculpted inside the spoon.
    - VC demitasse spoons (6), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      silverplate. 3 different styles
    - VC engraved teaspoon, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      silverplate. engraved with "E. B. V. E."
    - VC engraved teaspoon, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      silverplate. engraved with "S. W. N."
    - VC engraved teaspoons (7), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      silverplate, "Uncle Fred" spoons??. Monogrammed with unidentified students' initials. "M. L. McC." [Maria L. McClurg, Spec 1866-1867?]
    - VC forks (5), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 1)
      silver forks (5) with VC logo on handle
    - VC salt spoon, long-handled, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      silverplate
    - VC salt spoons (4), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
    - VC spoons, undated (Box 31)
      Sterling silver spoon with square edge and "VC" printed on handle. Silver salt spoon (?) with decorative handle, engraved with initials and "Vassar" inside the spoon. In red velvet case.
    - VC table spoons (2), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      sterling, VC logo on handle
    - VC teaspoon, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      sterling, VC logo on handle, curved handle
    - VC teaspoon, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      sterling, VC logo on handle, flat handle
    - VC teaspoon, Class of 1908, circa 1908 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      VC Senior Parlor teaspoon with "Schermerhorn '08" engraved on reverse. Belonged to Helen I. Schermerhorn (VC 1908).
    - VC teaspoon, Class of 1911, circa 1911 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      sterling, Class of 1911 logo on handle
    - VC teaspoon, Class of 1918, circa 1918 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      sterling, Class of 1918 logo on handle
    - VC teaspoon, Class of 1904 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      silverplate. engraved with "Mary Taylor 1904"
    - VC teaspoon, round, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
    - VC teaspoons (2), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      sterling. 2 different styles
    - VC teaspoons (5), undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
    - VC tongs, 1918 (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
      Silver sandwich tongs from 1918's Senior Parlor
  - Stationary and Paper Items
    - Citation for war service in France, 1919 Apr 19 (Box 93)
      Paper citation thanking Margaret Clark Neal for her service with the AEF.
    - Door block notes, circa 1915 (Box 99)
      Notes left by students at each other's dorm room doors.
    - Gum wrapper, undated (Box 10)
      Wrapper from a piece of gum, printed with text titled "Flirtation - Fan Flirtation No. 1" followed by instructions on how to use a fan to flirt. Features a line that says "Let the Vassar girl lend an ear."
    - Passport, 1878
      Passport issued by U.S. State Department to Ella Dodge (VC 1876)
    - Prospectus of Vassar Female College from Godey's Lady's Magazine, 1865; [Framed; 2 copies] (Box 83)
    - Sign for Alumnae Library, undated; [Framed] (On shelf)
      From the Alumnae/i House?
    - Street car schedule for Vassar College, undated; [Framed] (Box 89 (Oversize))
      "City Rail Road - Cars Leave Vassar College..." Printed schedule, framed.
    - VC calendar, 1988 (Box 29)
      VC calendar
    - VC class scrolls (3), undated (Box 53)
      3 "joke" scrolls
    - VC handkerchief box (?), undated (Box 82)
      cardboard box with an illustration of a "Vassar girl" labeled "Vassar Lawn"
    - VC menu, 1894 (Box 67)
      Decorative Menu, June 12, 1894
    - VC notepads, undated (Box 29)
      VC notepad "Alumnae House"
    - VC notepads, 1986 (Box 29)
      VC notepad "Inaugural '86"
    - VC stickers, undated (Box 29)
      Stickers, pink and gray VC pennants
  - Technology
    - Audograph index strips, French Department, between 1904 and 1920 (Box 72)
      Audograph index strips used by French Department for language instruction.
    - Audograph vinyl disks, French Department, between 1904 and 1920 (Box 73)
      Audograph vinyl recording disks used by French Department for language instruction.
    - Graphophone audio player, French Department, between 1904 and 1920 (Box 71)
      Graphophone wax cylinder player in wooden carrying case, device inside box is in disrepair. wax cylinders, and Audograph vinyl recording disks (2 boxes) used by French Department for language instruction
    - Miniature binoculars (3), undated (Box 67)
      three small miniature binoculars, two with images of Main Building, one with the Philadelphia exhibition of 1876
    - Stereographs - Natural History, circa 1870 (Box 6)
      Set of "Hurst's Stereoscopic Studies of Natural History, for Schools and Parlor Entertainments," published circa 1870, housed in beautiful wooden box with engraved plate reading "Vassar College." Appear to all be images of natural history exhibits at the Free Museum in Albany, NY. Included note reads "Thought to have been in Main Parlor."
    - Stereographs - VC Art Gallery, circa 1877 (Box 6)
      6 views of the Vassar College Art Gallery (circa 1877?), taken and published by Slee Brothers Photographers in Poughkeepsie. Includes duplicates.
    - Stereographs - VC Museum of Natural History, circa 1877 (Box 6)
      3 views of the Vassar College Museum of Natural History (circa 1877?), taken and published by Slee Brothers Photographers in Poughkeepsie. Includes duplicates.
    - Typewriter, Chemistry Department, undated (On shelf)
      Typewriter with wooden base and metal cover secured with 4 latches. Reputed to be the oldest on campus, came from the Chemistry Department
    - Typewriter, Ruth Fulton Benedict, undated (On shelf)
      portable Corona typewriter used on her field trips
    - VC library paper embosser, undated (Box 67)
      Handheld metal paper embosser, embosses "Vassar College Library."
    - VC mechanical stamp, undated (Box 14)
    - Wax cylinder, undated (Box 14)
      Edison gold molded record of the Vassar Girls Quartette
    - Wax cylinders, French Department, between 1904 and 1920 (Box 72)
      Wax cylinders used by French Department for language instruction
  - Textiles
    - Bag, 1913 (Box 59)
      Class of 1913 bag, blue felt with white lettering
    - Blanket, circa 1913 (Box 87 (Oversize))
      pink wool blanket with V's on it
    - Clothing - Academic robe, undated (Box 5)
      Black velvet academic robe that belonged to Sarah Gibson Blanding. Made by Cotrell & Leonard.
    - Clothing - Apron, undated (Box 91 (Oversize))
      Green apron with black edging, Class of 1911
    - Clothing - Baccalaureate Hood, undated (Box 17)
      Black with white velvet and pink ribbon stripes.
    - Clothing - Baccalaureate Hood, [1906?] (Box 49)
      Baccalaureate Hood made by Cottrel & Leonard, Albany N.Y. Belonged to Ethel M. Fair (VC 1906)?
    - Clothing - Baccalaureate Hood, 1904 (Box 49)
      Baccalaureate Hood of Elisabeth W. Allen, VC 1904, made by Ede & Ravenscroft.
    - Clothing - Baccalaureate Hood, circa 1910 (Box 101 (Oversize))
      VC Class of 1910 graduation hood made by E. Moore Company Chicago. Gown missing?
    - Clothing - Bloomers, undated (Box 79)
      VC Class of 1953 rose and gray bloomers
    - Clothing - Bonnet, undated (Box 24)
      Class of 1911 bonnet
    - Clothing - Christening Dress, undated (Box 101 (Oversize))
      Christening dress of Cornelia Marjorie D. MacCracken, cream/beige with tassels and shawl.
    - Clothing - Class Day Dress, circa 1913 (Box 28)
      VC Class Day dress that belonged to Harriet Bradley Fitt, VC 1913
    - Clothing - Class Day Dress, 1932 (Box 64)
      Class Day dress, pink, of Elizabeth (Fish) Wright, VC 1932.
    - Clothing - Commencement Dress, 1907 (Box 76 (Oversize))
      White cotton lace commencement dress and petticoat worn by Eleanor Brinsmade, VC 1907
    - Clothing - Commencement Dress, 1878 (Box 90 (Oversize))
      Commencement dress, pale blue-green satin, worn by Laura (Huntington) Brown, VC 1878. Dress consists of a skirt, top, 2 lace sleeves, and decorative maroon and gray ribbons.
    - Clothing - Commencement Dress, 1911 (Box 101 (Oversize))
      Commencement dress, cream with tassels and beaded collar, of Mary E. Carter, VC 1911
    - Clothing - Daisy Chain Dress, 1906 (Box 75 (Oversize))
      White cotton and lace Daisy Chain dress in two pieces, worn by Edith (Start) Hurd (VC 1908).
    - Clothing - Daisy Chain Dress, circa 1913 (Box 28)
      VC Daisy Chain dress that belonged to Harriet Bradley Fitt, VC 1913
    - Clothing - Graduation cap, 1970 (Box 28)
      Graduation cap with peace sign pinned to it
    - Clothing - Graduation cap, 1896 (Box 53)
      VC mortarboard of Alice Howland, VC 1896
    - Clothing - Graduation cap, gown, and hood, circa 1990-2000 (Box 87 (Oversize))
      VC graduation clothing
    - Clothing - Gym clothes, 1939 (Box 64)
      Blue cotton one piece "leotard" and separate blue cotton brief skirt, made by Wright and Ditson for 1939 Vassar College Freshman "Body Mechanics" Class. Belonged to Anne (Reed) Dean (VC 1943).
    - Clothing - Gym suit, circa 1914 (Box 101 (Oversize))
      VC gym suit, black (in 2 pieces). One-piece jumpsuit with "'14" in pink felt on the back and matching black skirt.
    - Clothing - Gym suit, undated (Box 8)
      VC tan gabardine gym suit
    - Clothing - Gym suit pants, circa 1916 (Box 49)
      Navy blue gym suit pants belonging to Margaret Beard Gilpin (VC 1916)
    - Clothing - Gym suits (2), circa 1908 (Box 96 (Oversize))
      2 VC gym suits, wool, dark blue with dark green trim. Each outfit consists of a long-sleeve button-up shirt and baggy pants. One pair of pants has the name "M. C. Nelson(?)" on the inside and the other has "M. Stager(?)"
    - Clothing - Hat, circa 1990-2000 (Box 65)
      VC reunion hat, straw with maroon hat band, owned by Margarete Midas Meyers, VC 1948/1949
    - Clothing - [Hat band?], undated (Box 24)
      Class of 1911 hat band(?)
    - Clothing - Jacket, 1938 (Box 87 (Oversize))
      White cotton/dungaree buttoned jacket, presumably worn by Laura West, VC 1914 at a 1938 VC reunion
    - Clothing - Long sleeve shirt, 1984 (Box 57)
      Seven Sisters Tennis Championship, green shirt with long sleeves.
    - Clothing - Masks, 2020 (Box 62)
      Five masks printed with Vassar logo and scenes issued as precaution against COVID-19.
    - Clothing - Mittens, circa 1935 (Box 91 (Oversize))
      VC Class of 1935 mittens, red white and blue woolen mittens with 1935 on them
    - Clothing - Scarf, circa 1947 (Box 32)
      Blue scarf with Cornaro Window design
    - Clothing - Scarf, circa 1940s (Box 24)
      Scarf showing pendants of Vassar, Radcliffe, Smith, Bryn Mawr and other women’s colleges.
    - Clothing - Scarf, circa 1990-2000 (Box 91 (Oversize))
      silk scarf with images of the Vassar campus
    - Clothing - Scarf, 1945 (Box 32)
      VC 50th reunion scarf, cream, stenciled "96"
    - Clothing - Scarf, undated (Box 24)
      Thin blue scarf with white "VC" logo.
    - Clothing - Scarf, undated (Box 24)
      Thin red scarf with "VC" logo on one end and outline of Main Building on the other.
    - Clothing - Scarf, 1986; [Framed] (Framed Storage 2.8)
      Scarf, yellow, printed with Cornaro Window design (Lorenzo Silk Creations)
    - Clothing - Shirt, undated (Box 91 (Oversize))
      Yellow and green basketball jersey worn by VC WWII veteran [wool?]
    - Clothing - Sweater, undated (Box 12)
      VC Varsity sweater, gray
    - Clothing - Sweatshirt, undated (Box 97)
      Heathered gray sweatshirt with red and black Vassar College logo on chest and left sleeve.
    - Clothing - Sweatshirt, circa 1964 (Box 74)
      Light gray heathered sweatshirt with Vassar seal in pink.
    - Clothing - Swimsuit, undated (Box 96 (Oversize))
      Marathon swimsuit - Vassar(?), used circa 1948-1968.
    - Clothing - Tie, circa 1964 (Box 9)
      Pink tie with cornaro window design. Has some stains.
    - Clothing - T-Shirt, [1989?] (Box 57)
      Africana Studies 20th Anniversary t-shirt, red with print of a piece of African art.
    - Clothing - T-Shirt, 1992 (Box 57)
      Class of 1987 reunion t-shirt, white with maroon print.
    - Clothing - T-Shirt, 1989 (Box 57)
      Founder's day t-shirt, white with black print on front and back. "20 Coed Years at Vassar - What a Long and Strange Trip It's Been"
    - Clothing - T-Shirt, 1992 (Box 48)
      Founder's Day, White shirt with print of Matthew Vassar and "More Than a Brewer"
    - Clothing - T-Shirt, undated (Box 48)
      Gray t-shirt with VC centennial seal printed in black
    - Clothing - T-Shirt, circa 1990s (Box 48)
      Light gray t-shirt with maroon print of Thompson Library and "So Many Books, So Little Time"
    - Clothing - T-Shirt, 1988 (Box 57)
      Vassar College Women's Weekend t-shirt, white with black image and text "Act Up!"
    - Clothing - T-shirt, undated (Box 92)
      Green Co+ed=VC t-shirt
    - Clothing - T-shirt, 1999 (Box 79)
      T-shirt, heather gray with maroon print: "1949-1999, Vassar Book Sale, Vassar Club of Washington, D.C., We Turn Used Books into a College Education"
    - Clothing - T-shirt, 1997 (Box 17)
      VC Earth Day t-shirt, tan with green print. On back is a quote from Annie Dillard
    - Clothing - T-shirt, 1992 (Box 92)
      VC Founder's Day t-shirt
    - Clothing - T-shirt, 1980-1981 (Box 92)
      WVKR-fm Poughkeepsie Free Radio, white t-shirt
    - Clothing - T-shirt (2), 2007 May (Box 17)
      2 Founder's Day t-shirts, dark blue, on theme of Disney's Fantasia. Image is Matthew Vassar With Disney's Wizard's Hat.
    - Clothing - Visor (4), 1970 (Box 25)
      maroon visors with VC '70 in grey letters
    - Diploma ribbons, undated (Box 10)
      Pink ribbons used to tie VC diplomas.
    - Green Drape, undated (Box 91 (Oversize))
      Class of 1910 or 1911
    - Handkerchief, undated (Box 48)
      VC handkerchief
    - Handkerchief, undated (Box 59)
      Class of 1957 45th reunion, white handkerchief with green letters and images of Vassar buildings
    - Monogrammed pillow case, circa 1964 (Box 74)
      White with red embroidery. Belonged to Gail R. Becker (VC 1964).
    - Napkins (3), 1918 (Box 32)
      3 white, lace napkins embroidered with the seal of the Class of 1918.
    - Pillow, 1985 (Box 97)
      VC Class of 1960 25th reunion pillow, stuffed with t-shirts given as favors
    - Pillow top, undated (Box 24)
      orange and pink pillow cover with images of Main building
    - Pillow top, 1906 (Box 24)
      white and blue pillow top with scenes of VC buildings
    - Ribbon - Pinned, 1933 Aug 26 (Box 67)
      "Dutchess County Welcomes President Franklin D. Roosevelt" VC Aide Pin
    - Ribbons, undated (Box 32)
      rose and grey gros-grain (silk) ribbons used to tie Vassar College diplomas
    - Tablecloth, 1913 (Box 28)
      VC 1913, tan tablecloth, scalloped edges, embroidered with gold and rose thread
    - Torah cover, white satin, undated (Box 5)
      Belonged to VC faculty member, Jean Charlemagne Bracq(?)
    - Tote bag, 1913 (Box 48)
      blue canvas reunion bag
    - Tote bag, 2000 (Box 79)
      Cream canvas tote bag from "VC Parents Weekend 14-16 April 2000"
    - Tote bag, 1993 Oct 8-9 (Box 91 (Oversize))
      Environmental Sciences Forum Tote Bag
    - Tote bag, 1980 (Box 17)
      Heavy, tan cotton tote bag from "Books in Search of Children" conference at VC
    - Tote bag, undated (Box 17)
      VC canvas bag with checkerboard pattern of blue Vassar seals
    - Tote bag, undated (Box 91 (Oversize))
      white canvas tote bag with blue handles, image of Ferry house and words "Ferry House 55 years"
    - VC seal on fabric, undated (Box 24)
      White square of fabric with the Vassar seal printed in pink.
  - Toys and Games
    - Card game, circa 1882 (Box 51)
      "Le Jeu des Academiciens" presented to the President of Vassar College by the French class of 1882 and Professor R. See.
    - Card game, circa 1880 (Box 51)
      "Le Jeu des Mythologie" dedicated to H.W. Webster by the French class of 1880 and Professor R. See.
    - Doll, 1858 (Box 95 (Oversize))
      Doll with Greiner head, wearing a faded calico dress. Includes a small copy of a book "Food for Christians" and two fabric flowers. Accession record reads: "Doll was dressed to represent 'Miss Vassar 1865' for display by the Worcester College Club in a doll show. She was an old family doll owned by Cynthia Carey of Worcester, MA."
    - VC playing cards (2), undated (Box 29)
      unopened - 2 packs
  - Wooden Objects
    - Class of 1900, folding sign or table (?), undated (On shelf)
      Wooden disk, painted yellow and printed with "1900," has legs and folds so that the disk is flat like a table instead of upright like a sign. one arm appears broken.
    - Decoupage box with scene of VC, undated (Box 99)
      Round, wooden decoupage box painted with a scene of Vassar College.
    - Room draw numbers, undated (Box 24)
      wooden blocks placed in a box and pulled for rooms in the dorms. Only a sampling.
    - VC bootjack, undated (Box 50)
      wooden bootjack [supposed to have hung from student's doors]
    - VC bootjack, undated (Box 50)
    - VC bootjacks (4), undated (Box 50)
      wooden bootjacks [supposed to have hung from student's doors]
    - VC seal, circa 1968 (Box 84)
      Pink Vassar College seal printed on round mdf fiberboard.
    - VC Souvenir Box (2), 1926 (Box 60)
      souvenir boxes (2) painted red with Vassar scenes. "Vassar College in 1865"
    - Wooden Gavel with metal plaque attached, circa 1989 (Box 14)
      Wooden gavel with metal plaque reading: "Jeanne Schock Vassar Student Association President 1988-1989"
- Series III. Miscellaneous and Historical Objects, circa 1648 - [1917?]
  - Certificate, 1855 (Box 93)
    Certificate of admittance(?) to Poughkeepsie Female Collegiate Institute for Charlotte Tallman.
  - Chair, child's, undated (On shelf)
    child's small wooden rocking chair
  - Fans (5), undated (Box 56)
    Decorative, handheld folding fans.
  - Jewelry - Memory beads, undated (Box 10)
    Set of memory beads in a box of E. Faber Pocket Pencils.
  - Medal - Albany Centennial, 1786 (Box 26)
    Commemorates the 100th anniversary of Albany, NY
  - Medal - Paris Exposition, 1900 (Box 26)
    Paris exposition medal, for exhibition on women in higher education put together by Elizabeth M. Howe collaborating with the Association of Collegiate Alumnae. Includes accompanying letter.
  - Medals - Paris Exposition (3), 1900 (Box 53)
    Paris exposition medals (3). Three different medals set in a wooden plaque.
  - Medal - Yale, 1901 (Box 26)
    Yale University 200th anniversary medal
  - Miniature portrait, undated (Box 26)
    Portrait of a young woman by [H. Harding?] in red wooden case.
  - Miniature portrait, undated (Box 26)
    Portrait of a young woman in red velvet frame.
  - Paper dolls, circa 1850s, 1870s (Box 10)
    2 paper dolls with assorted outfits. One doll includes an envelope labeled "Amusements for Little Girls. Lizzie," and is published by McLoughlin Brothers Manufacturers, 24 Beekman St, NY.
  - Pepper shaker, undated (Box 1, Section 03)
    Mahogany. Exposed glue on one side--perhaps missing a piece.
  - Piece of wooden window, circa 1648 (Box 1, Section 06)
    "Piece of wood from the window through which Charles I attempted to make his escape." Circa 1648.
  - Plaster replica of WWI monument designed by Louis Majorelle, [1917?] (Box 97)
    Plaster (?) replica sculpture of Louis Marjorelle's memorial monument to the first three American soldiers killed in the First World War: James Bethel Gresham, Thomas Enright, and Merle Hay.
  - Reproduction of the Miracle at Cana, undated (Realia Box 11)
    Reproduction by F. Parsons of 11th Century Byzantine Art depicting two scenes from the life of Jesus in the collection of the Victoria and Albert Museum, London.
  - Reproduction of a Panel of a Book Cover, undated (Realia Box 11)
    Reproduction by F. Parsons of 12th Century Byzantine Art in the collection of the Victoria and Albert Museum, London. Top right corner broken.
  - Teaspoon, silver, undated (Blue Hagarty Silver Bag No. 2)
    Sterling, engraved "Roberta"
  - Vase, undated (Box 71)
    Large, round ceramic vase, white with blue glaze and chipped black paint around the top and bottom. Depicts an East-Asian style landscape scene.
  - Wooden gavel with metal plaque attached, undated (Box 14)
    Wooden gavel with metal plaque reading: "Made of the elm under which in 1775 George Washington assumed command of the Continental Army"